Inventory of the Overseas Weekly photographs
Hoover Institution Archives
Overseas Weekly photographs
1966-1971
2014C35
Hoover Institution Archives
12 oversize boxes, 1,851 digital image files (7.2 linear feet, 6.6 GB)
Negatives and contact sheets depicting scenes from the Vietnam War and American servicemen in Vietnam. Digital copies of select records also available at https://digitalcollections.hoover.org.
Overseas Weekly.
Access
Originals closed. Digital copies of select records available at https://digitalcollections.hoover.org.
Acquisition Information
Materials were acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 2014.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Alternate Forms Available
Digital copies of select records also available at https://digitalcollections.hoover.org.
Historical Note
Alternative newspaper aimed at American servicemen published during the Vietnam War.
Scope and Content of Collection
Negatives and contact sheets depicting scenes from the Vietnam War and American servicemen in Vietnam.
Overseas Weekly covered themes including American military action, humanitarian efforts, and the conditions of the Vietnamese civilians affected by the war. Each negative or contact sheet is accompanied by a typed summary describing the images written by the photographer and submitted to the editors of the publication. These caption sheets have been transcribed and the text maintained as the primary description for the images.
Vietnam War, 1961-1975--Pictorial works.
- Contact Sheet 10822, 1969 July 26
  Scope and Contents note
  Contact sheet containing 11 images.
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - action - Ben Het.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Sp5 David L. Minard washing head of Vietnamese baby - Capt. (Dr.) William F. Schneble? With baby.
- Contact Sheet 10823, circa 1967-1971
  Contact sheet containing 10 images.
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - No. 2 - Civil Affairs team.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Capt. Bill Hughes - Capt. Donald M. Savage - Pfc. Ronald Chandler - Destruction in village Gia An.
- Contact Sheet 10824, circa 1967-1971
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: 108-24 - Sp5 David L. Minard washing baby's head - Dr. Schneble - Sgt. Lyle Christy with machine gun.
- Contact Sheet 10825, circa 1967-1971
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: C Btry., 1st Bn., 30th Arty. (Capt. Jimmies S. Fears, Battery Commander).
- Contact Sheet 10826, circa 1967-1971
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Shots taken from helicopter, around Bong Son - Sp5 Claude Swearingen - Chief Warrant Officer George Cox - little boy washing car - Sgt. Chuck Lowenhagen - 3d Brig. Pio with Maggie, the mule - 1st Air Cavalry mascot - Terminal at An Kie air strip.
- Contact Sheet 10827, circa 1967-1971
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Play girls - at forward aid station, at 3d Brig. Cp. - Pfc. Charles Jenkins (with shirt off).
- Contact Sheet 10828, circa 1967-1971
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Maj. Gen. Harry W. O. Kinnard - Maj. Gen. Stanley Larsen - Mortar crew - VC [Viet Cong] suspects being led across field - firing at Bird.
- Contact Sheet 10829, circa 1967-1971
  Contact sheet containing 12 images.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: L.Z. Bird, 3d Brig - Sp5 Archie Schre? - medic with ? - Captured VC [Viet Cong] ammo - VC suspects carrying a dead VC in hammock.
- Contact Sheet 10830, circa 1967-1971
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Pfc. Michael Grant - Sp4 Louis Rodriguez - Col. H. B. (Hal) Moore.
- Contact Sheet 10831, circa 1967-1971
  Contact sheet containing 13 images.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: GIs walking through rubber plantation - Women, children drawing water from a well.
- Contact Sheet 10832, circa 1967-1971
  Contact sheet containing 16 images.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Sgt. Maj. B. M. Leblanc (with body of VC [Viet Cong]) - wreckage of APC - Ann Bryan with Pfc. James Bowling.
- Contact Sheet 10833, circa 1967-1971
  Contact sheet containing 18 images.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Camp Alpha - Housing in Vietnam.
- Contact Sheet 10834, circa 1967-1971
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Kids - Shoe shine boy - Black market.
- Contact Sheet 10835, circa 1967-1971
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Women & children on street.
- Contact Sheet 10836, circa 1967-1971
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Plaza BEQ - Girls selling cigarettes.
- Contact Sheet 10838, circa 1967-1971
  Contact sheet containing 7 images.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Girl with sugar cane cubes on her head - People picking up supplies at foster parents headquarters.
- Contact Sheet 10862, 1966 March
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Ann - No. 7900.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Black market stands on a Saigon street (mostly cigarettes) - Tu Do street scenes - Pedicabs.
- Contact Sheet 10864, circa 1967-1971
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: GI carrying wounded child.
- Contact Sheet 10864 (2), circa 1967-1971
  Contact sheet containing 24 images.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Operation Honolulu at Cu Chi - Sgt Michael S. Hirsch with boys - Sgt Maj Marvin Manning.
- Contact Sheet 10927, 1966 March 20
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Buddhist orphanage.
- Contact Sheet 10928, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Lee Echols - 1 x Ann.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Girls in Ao Dai - special services swimming pool - Lee Echols wearing her Ao Dai - pagoda at Buddhist institute.
- Contact Sheet 10961, 1966 April 8
  Contact sheet containing 4 images.
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Krause, Patty - Pfc. Bill Ambler - April 8, 66 O.F.
- Contact Sheet 11029, circa 1967-1971
  Contact sheet containing 15 images.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Sfc. David M. Palmer pointing & playing with kids - Sgt. Gordon Bowman with nurse - Capt. John Eliot (watching medics).
- Contact Sheet 11031, circa 1967-1971
  Contact sheet containing 21 images.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Vietnam - Poll - Buddhist funeral.
- Contact Sheet 11032, circa 1967-1971
  Contact sheet containing 17 images.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Sgt. Virgil Butcher - Capt. George M. Downs.
- Contact Sheet 11033, circa 1967-1971
  Contact sheet containing 22 images.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Sgt. Ronald E. Nilson - Lt. Col. Leonard L. Lewayne - 1st Lt. Don G. Christian.
- Contact Sheet 11034, circa 1967-1971
  Contact sheet containing 19 images.
- Contact Sheet 11035, circa 1967-1971
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Ann Bryan - George Gaspard.
- Contact Sheet 11036, circa 1967-1971
  Contact sheet containing 38 images.
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - village life - Montagnards.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Village life - Montagnard.
- Contact Sheet 11143, circa 1967-1971
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Street fighting on Saigon between MPs and civilian.
- Contact Sheet 11144, circa 1967-1971
  Contact sheet containing 23 images.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: A - Karen Walters - Diane Bloodhart / B - Can Tho Pier - hospital - ward of prostitutes.
- Contact Sheet 11145, circa 1967-1971
  Contact sheet containing 20 images.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Saigon Harbor - Sp5 Andy Anderson.
- Contact Sheet 11146, circa 1967-1971
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Lt. Col. William J. Maddox Jr. - Can Tho market and river front.
- Contact Sheet 11147, circa 1967-1971
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Can Tho market.
- Contact Sheet 11320, circa 1967-1971
  Contact sheet containing 35 images.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Soldiers hold back villagers crowding in for food and clothes - Doctor Helwig treats village woman - Soldiers distribute clothes & food - Aerial shots of Saigon - GIs passing out food & clothes.
- Contact Sheet 11321, circa 1967-1971
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Tunnel, in front at right - hands on hip, Lt. Col. Schultz - Tattoo (girl on soldier's arm) Soldiers pass out food & clothes.
- Contact Sheet 11322, 1966 May
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - 25th Inf. Div. base camp mortar team.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: 25th Inf. Div. Base Camp on Cu Chi plain - Soldier looks at captured Chi Com [Chinese Communist] - claymore mine - Mortella's mortar morticians (who operate a counter-mortar radar rig) - Mortar team in battalion base camp.
- Contact Sheet 11323, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - E/A - tunnel soldiers on patrol - Capt. Deliz.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Soldiers on patrol - Tunnel - Capt. Deliz.
- Contact Sheet 11324, circa 1967-1971
  Contact sheet containing 33 images.
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Co. B passing through village - Fort Smith operation - 1st Sgt. Samuel - Otis Holbrook.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: (c): Fort Smith Operation - 1st Sgt. Samuel Om's Holbrook III of Co. B - B Co. passing through village - (D): Fort Smith Operation - cows & water buffaloes.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: GI with kids - Pfc.Gerald Ruther, 21, with RPG-2 rocket launcher captured from VC [ Viet Cong ]. Both the Russians and the Chicoms [Chinese Communists] make this weapon - 1st Lt. Hamor Hanson, 24, with rifle captured from VC [Viet Cong] (14a-15a) S. Sgt. Henry Lawson (17-21) Howell with Capt. Roy Gilbert (22): Howell in mess hall (23) No good (14-27) Howell and Capt. Gilbert (left), Capt. Kenneth Joddin (28) Howell and Gilbert / Contact sheet B (30a) no good (31a-33a) Howell and Pfc. Dale Edwards. Capt. Joddin is in background. They're in jeep. (34a-35a) Howell on firing range. (36a-37a) Howell and 2d Lt. Timothy Ganahl, 24, on firing range. (OA4) Howell with Ganahl. (5-8) Howell with Pfc. Edwards. (9-15) Howell (16 through end) Wild shots of Vietnamese children taken at Phuoc Vinh / Contact sheet C: Fort Smith operation story - (27-29) Soldiers passing through a village. This is B company. (30-31) B Co. 1st Sgt. Samuel Otis Holbrook III. Cloth hanging out of helmet is to keep ants and bugs off his neck when he walks through brush./ Contact sheet D: Operation Fort Smith story (0-1) Two Gis at door of commo van. (2-10) Taken from APC which made a short patrol outside battalion base camp. Kids along highway (in 6a) are friendly. (11) Young businessmen outside basecamp perimeter. (12-13) Vietnamese civic action team. (14-26) More shots of Co. B going through villages. Gis shy away from skittish cows and water buffalo. That's a water buffalo woman is holding in 22A.
- Contact Sheet 11325, 1966 June
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Lt. Col. Edward - Jack Foisie (lammer) - Ronnessen (NBC) - Pvt. Adam R. Weber.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: 11323 - E - Fort Smith operation - Sp4 Loren Tomblin found bunch of bananas - VC [Viet Cong] suspect is lead to APC- GIs dumping garbage after chow.
- Contact Sheet 11326, 1966 May 26
  Contact sheet containing 39 images.
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Acting 1st Sgt. Ronald J. Guerin Co. B - soldier drying socks & boots - troops break open C rations - machine gunners & platoon leader to go aboard helicopter.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Contact sheet B: (0-6) Troops break open C rations at noon / Contact sheet C: (10-11) Machine gunner waits to get aboard helicopter for move to new LZ. (13) Platoon leader waits to get aboard chopper. (15-20) Troops on LZ savoy waiting for move to LZ Clemson. (24-26) Same machine gunner. (30) Soui Ca valley from the air. (31-34) Acting 1st Sgt. Ronald J. Guerin, of B Co., 2/ 8th, cautiously checks out basket troops found in high grass near LZ Clemson. But instead of a booby trap he found basket of rice, which he destroyed. He is from company which is subject of OW story. This photo taken 10 days after action described in story. (35-36) Soldier takes advantage of a few free hours on LZ Clemson to dry out socks and boots. (37) GI rests on LZ Clemson.
- Contact Sheet 11327, 1966 May 26
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - choppers bring in hot breakfast - troopers in rain.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: (0-1) Choppers bring in hot breakfast to LZ Savoy. (2) Cook stands by containers of hot chow. (5) Troopers stand by C rations also unloaded from breakfast choppers. (6-8) Troops get hot breakfast from field chow line. (10-12) Troops stand around in rain on LZ Savoy. (13) Correspondent cowers in helicopter while troops stand in rain. (15-19) Troops in the rain on LZ Savoy. (20-21) At noon soldiers break open C rations.
- Contact Sheet 11328, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Pfc. Vance Sneed - Sgt. Albert O'Donnell - Sgt. Lee Brown Jr. on guard at stream - Sgt. Ronald A. Koebbe - Sgt. Joseph F. Hartin shave - Pfc. Joe Brown cleans rifle - Sgt. Henry Roach - Sp. Howard V. Rowe.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Contact sheet E: (9-10) Pfc. Vance Sneed (left) and Sgt. Albert O'Donnell at LZ Clemson. (16-17) Sgt. Lee Brown Jr. (foreground) on guard at stream on one end of LZ Clemson. (18) Sgt. Joseph F. Hartin (cq) shaves at LZ Clemson. (23-24) Pfc. Joe Brown cleans M16 at LZ Clemson. (27-29) 1st Sgt. Ronald A. Koebbe (for story on B Co., 2/8). (30-32) Sgt. Henry Roach (for story on B Co., 2/8) (33-36) Sfc. Howard V. Rowe (for story on B Co., 2/8). (last two shots) Typical street scene at Camp Radcliff.
- Contact Sheet 11329, 1966 May 20
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Capt. Douglas Auer - Lt. Col. Edward Fenig - Maj. James K. Schumaker - black market - Capt. Raymond K. Wicker.
- Contact Sheet 11330-1, circa 1967-1971
  Contact sheet containing 32 images.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Schumaker trial - Capt. James E. Baker (defense) - Capt. Raymond K. Wicker - Capt. Edward S. Molnar (ass. def.) - GI leaves Saigon bar with hostess - woman in ao dai crossing street - front of another bar - Captiol Bar, one of Tu Do's finest - bars in Saigon - front of Capitol bar - kid on stool is doorman.
- Contact Sheet 11332-1, circa 1967-1971
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: 11331: Sign outside HQ of 765th Trans. BN - Cam Mickelson talking to MP - Vietnamese-American marriage (mother husband) / 11332 - Red Cross girls - from left: Liz Miller, Sandy Tosselman and Jane Puffer (1) Joan Puffer (2-4 ) Liz Miller (5-8) Nancy Kelly plays cards with Gis - from left: Liz, Sandy, Joan.
- Contact Sheet 11333, circa 1967-1971
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Sp4 Bill Barcday - Laundry - Local girls - Lt. & Mrs. R. A. Williams.
- Contact Sheet 11431, circa 1967-1971
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Vietnam - Black market.
- Contact Sheet 11432, circa 1967-1971
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Vietnam - Poll - Black market - woman?
- Contact Sheet 11433, circa 1967-1971
  Contact sheet containing 36 images.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Saigon Harbor.
- Contact Sheet 11434, circa 1967-1971
  Contact sheet containing 28 images.
- Contact Sheet 11435, circa 1967-1971
  Contact sheet containing 30 images.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Vietnam - Saigon Harbor - An Khe street scenes.
- Contact Sheet 11487, circa 1967-1971
  Contact sheet containing 31 images.
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - suspected VCs, taken prisoner - GIs repair tents after Cu Chi mortar attack.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Suspected VC [Viet Cong] are taken prisoner - Rebuilding of tents damaged in mortar attack.
- Contact Sheet 11488, circa 1967-1971
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Girl sells peanuts at plaza gate with MP on duty - Airplane BOQ - Marion Rospach.
- Contact Sheet 11488x, circa 1967-1971
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: F: girl sells peanuts at plaza gate with MP on duty - G: airplane - BOQ - Marion Rospach.
- Contact Sheet 11489, circa 1967-1971
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Cu Chi mortar attack - Cage in POW compound - Small boy suspected VC [Viet Cong] messenger - Lt. Col. George S. Black, 25th Div. PM - 1st Lt. Frank Stone OIC of POW compound - E - VC prisoners blindfolded and handed over to MP - GIs playing with a python at Tan Son Nhut AB.
- Contact Sheet 11519, 1966 August 21
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Ann Bryan - Pfc. Joe Shipman - Pvt. Joe Cizmarik - A/2C Steve Slovik - Recreation in Taiwan.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Vietnam - recreation in Taiwan - August 1966.
- Contact Sheet 11586, circa 1967-1971
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Hospitalman Mr. & Mrs. Charles H. Block - Mrs. Concepcion Riley, holding baby - Hospitals.
- Contact Sheet 11587, circa 1967-1971
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: S. Sgt. Jay Staver looks over holsters at Vietnamese shops - Hats - GIs with crash helmets - Marine Capt. E. D. Dauksz Danano.
- Contact Sheet 11588, circa 1967-1971
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Peasant riding on water buffalo - Capt. Hershel Gober talking to Capt. Nguyen Van Huynh - Fonce housing area - Gober playing with little boy "Pigpen" - Vietnamese children.
- Contact Sheet 11589, 1966 April 7
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - roll #2 - Ann B. - Capt. Hershel Gober (playing guitar) - Children in streets of Saigon.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Capt. Hershel Gober playing guitar - Children in streets of Saigon.
- Contact Sheet 11590, 1966 September
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - food shops - Lt. Col. Riddle - loading of food - Sp4 Edwin A. Long - fancy hat - GI with rifle - Sp4 John Morgan - Pfc. Hans Drews.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: GIs unloading food - Sp4 Edwin A. Long in village shop - Vietnamese peddle ware - Kids in shops - Sp4 John Morgan - Pfc. Hans Drews - Capt. Vic Letonoff.
- Contact Sheet 11591, 1966 September 11
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - 2d Lt. John R. Johnston - Sgt. William Silas - S. Sgt. Willie G. Glover.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Highway with mud - 2nd Lt. John R. Johnston Jr. - Sgt. William Silas Jr. - S. Sgt. Willie G. Glover.
- Contact Sheet 11592, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: .Vietnam - Pfc. Richard Brinkley - Pfc. William Black - 2d Lt. Ralph Harrison - Animals (scout dog story).
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Scout dog story - Pfc. Richard Brinkley - Pfc. William Black - 2nd Lt. Ralph Harrison.
- Contact Sheet 11593, 1966 September
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Red Cross - Marion Gibbs - Vicky Olson.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Red Cross girls - Marion Gibbs - Vicky Olson.
- Contact Sheet 11594, circa 1967-1971
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: 11594b: D - Red Cross girls during program - Sheila, Vicky & Pat - 11594b(1): A- Red Cross girls - Sheila Otto, Vicky Olson, Pat McDaniel - S Sgt Harry Jacobson.
- Contact Sheet 11595, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - uniforms US - fancy hats - A/2c Earl L. Morrison.
- Contact Sheet 11597, circa 1967-1971
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Body of man who looked Chinese - Soldiers guarding bodies - Lt. Reczek talking on radio.
- Contact Sheet 11598, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Pfc. Ronald House - Cpl. Harvey Sawyer - Sp5 John Goodwin - bodies - officers studying battle area - Lt. Reczek.
- Contact Sheet 11599, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - T. Sgt. Donald Mashburn - Capt. Norman Benson - Capt. Roger Heston - black market - mustache hair & beard.
- Contact Sheet 11600, 1966 October
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Howells - 1st Lt. Hamor Hanson - Capt. Rey Gilbert - Capt. Kenneth Jodi.
- Contact Sheet 11601, 1966 July
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Bryan - market in Bien Hoa - children on street - car wash - bars.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Market in Bien Hoa - Children on street - Car wash - Bars.
- Contact Sheet 11602, 1966 October
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Howells with 1st Bn., 2nd Inf.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Howell (the Vietnamese kid with the 1st Bn., 2nd inf.).
- Contact Sheet 11910, circa 1967-1971
  Contact sheet containing 29 images.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: News stands.
- Contact Sheet 11911, circa 1967-1971
  Contact sheet containing 37 images.
- Contact Sheet 11912, circa 1967-1971
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Chaplain Col. Harold O. Prudell - Lt. Cmdr. Bob Condon.
- Contact Sheet 11913, circa 1967-1971
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Christmas party - Sfc. James A. Taylor band leader.
- Contact Sheet 11914, circa 1967-1971
- Contact Sheet 11915, circa 1967-1971
  Contact sheet containing 27 images.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: Black market.
- Contact Sheet 11916, circa 1967-1971
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: X-Mas [Christmas] - Warrant Officer Richard Salzarulo (Santa).
- Contact Sheet 11917, circa 1967-1971
  Contact sheet containing 25 images.
  PHOTOGRAPHER'S DESCRIPTION: X- Mas [Christmas] - Sfc. James A. Taylor plays horn.
- Contact Sheet 11918, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - man on the street.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Photo id-2 - Contact sheet F. For man on street (0a) Sp4 Charles Knoop (1-2) Sgt. Thomas Sell (left) and S. Sgt. Raymond Coss (3-4) Sp4 Larry Boyd (5-6) Sgt. Hazel Hill (left) and Dorsey Weeks.
- Contact Sheet 11919, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Bryan - GIs listen to radio while filling sandbags - spray flights - Capt. Edwin Ross.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Film 1: I went on a second Ranch Hand flight to get more pictures, in case you wanted to reuse that story in an early Pacific edition … Most of two undeveloped rolls of film in this package were taken on the flight. (1-3) Two GIs at Cu Chi (25th Inf. Div.) listen to radio while filling sandbags. They are Pfc. Luby E. Smith, 22 (left) and Sp4 Paul A. Juchniewicz, 22, both of HQ & Hq Co., 4th Bn., 9th Inf., 25th Inf. Div. They were listening to the country and western show. This was taken for radio-tv story. Next two or three shots show C123 spray aircraft, preparing to take off on Ranch Hand flight; taken from cargo door of 123 in front of it. Next several shots show A/1C roscoe Jones, a flight mechanic sitting in his armor plate box in the rear of the spray plane. Last shots are close up of Capt. Edwin Ross, aircraft commander, on spray flight.
- Contact Sheet 11920, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Bryan - spray mission - Capt. Paul Knese.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Roll 2: Most of the roll are pics taken through cockpit window showing 123s in front on spray mission. Hopefully, you'll be able to see the spray coming out of the planes in some of the shots. Last pic is of Capt. Paul Knese, copilot, coming down out of cockpit.
- Contact Sheet 11921, 1966 July
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Ann - Marines relaxing - Martha Raye.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Rest of the roll are pictures for feature on Martha Raye (coming next week). There was such a jam I couldn't keep a list of pictures as I shot them. But Martha Raye is unmistakable (she's dressed in Lt. Col's uniform). Most are of her on stage or with sailors or Marines (show was at Naval Support Activity). First shot or two is of her squatting on floor, signing autographs (her autograph is enclosed; is present for OW staff). Only man who's name I have is sailor holding cake (toward end of roll). He is Commissaryman 2/C Rick Sommers, 27 / Roll II: For China Beach R& R story: (1-2) Three Marines from an anti-tank outfit relax under trees. They are (from left) Lance Cpl. Dewey Beatty, 18, Lance Cpl. Mike Coniger, 20, and Lance Cpl. Kenneth Larson, 18. (3-4) Lance Cpl. Richard Mohon, 21, 2d Bn., 1st Marines, gets a shave from Vietnamese barber. (5) Quarters for men stationed at R&R center. (6) Random shot of grounds of R&R center.
- Contact Sheet 11922, 1966 November 7
  Contact sheet containing 8 images.
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Ann - black market.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: First two shots are mugs of Vance. (1,2,3) Black market stands on Saigon street. Most are filled with PX cigarettes. (4-9) Tu Do street scenes. Last three are of pedicabs.
- Contact Sheet 11923, 1967 January
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Stokes - passengers waiting terminal at An Khe airstrip.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Use with GI waiting story. Pix are of passenger waiting terminal at An Khe airstrip. Disregard pix of chopper gunners and long distance shots…Hope the fingers are not evident this time. R. Stokes.
- Contact Sheet 11924, 1966 December 5
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Bryan - 1st Lt. Dale R. Crafton.
- Contact Sheet 11925, 1966 November 14
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Ann - Brig. Gen. John R. Deane - miscell. pics. in field.